<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>contribute on Stencil</title><link>https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/categories/contribute/</link><description>Recent content in contribute on Stencil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/categories/contribute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contribute to the Stencil Project</title><link>https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/contribute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/contribute/</guid><description>Stencil relies heavily on the enthusiasm and participation of the open-source community. We need your support in both its development and documentation.
Stencil&amp;rsquo;s contribution guidelines are detailed in a CONTRIBUTING.md in the Stencil source repository on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Contribute to Stencil Development</title><link>https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/contribute/development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/contribute/development/</guid><description>Introduction stencil is an open-source project and lives by the work of its contributors. There are plenty of open issues, and we need your help to make stencil even more awesome. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to be a Go guru to contribute to the project&amp;rsquo;s development.
Assumptions This contribution guide takes a step-by-step approach in hopes of helping newcomers. Therefore, we only assume the following:
You are new to Git or open-source projects in general You are a fan of Stencil and enthusiastic about contributing to the project If you&amp;rsquo;re struggling at any point in this contribution guide, reach out to the Stencil community in Stencil&amp;rsquo;s Discussion forum</description></item><item><title>Contribute to the Stencil Docs</title><link>https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/contribute/documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://getoutreach.github.io/stencil/contribute/documentation/</guid><description>Create Your Fork It&amp;rsquo;s best to make changes to the Stencil docs on your local machine to check for consistent visual styling. Make sure you&amp;rsquo;ve created a fork of [stencil](https://github.com/getoutreach/stencil on GitHub and cloned the repository locally on your machine. For more information, you can see GitHub&amp;rsquo;s documentation on &amp;ldquo;forking&amp;rdquo; or follow along with Stencil&amp;rsquo;s development contribution guide.
You can then create a separate branch for your additions. Be sure to choose a descriptive branch name that best fits the type of content.</description></item></channel></rss>