<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Stencil</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Stencil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apache License</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/about/license/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/about/license/</guid><description>Version 2.0, January 2004 https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
Terms and Conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution
1. Definitions “License” shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.
“Licensor” shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.
“Legal Entity” shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity.</description></item><item><title>What is Stencil?</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/about/what-is-stencil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/about/what-is-stencil/</guid><description>Stencil is a tool to eliminate run-once boilerplate code generally created by tools like create-react-app and eliminate the decade old practice of copying and pasting boilerplate from stackoverflow and other websites.
Instead you can write modules for your boilerplate and other &amp;ldquo;components&amp;rdquo; of an application, library, or etc and use them in your application/library/whatever else you dare to create.
Stencil enables this through a few different components:
Modules - The major selling point of stencil, allows you to create module groups of Go templates and other dependencies.</description></item></channel></rss>