<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>getting started on Stencil</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/categories/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in getting started on Stencil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/categories/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get Started</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/</guid><description>If this is your first time using Stencil and you&amp;rsquo;ve already installed Stencil on your machine, we recommend the quick start.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/quick-start/</guid><description>This quick start uses macOS in the examples. For instructions about how to install Stencil on other operating systems, see install.
It is required to have Git installed to run this tutorial.
Step 1: Install Stencil If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have stencil installed, follow the documentation to install it.
Step 2: Create a service.yaml First start by creating a new directory for your application, this should generally match whatever the name for your application is going to be.</description></item><item><title>Install Stencil</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/installing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/installing/</guid><description>There is lots of talk about &amp;ldquo;Stencil being written in Go&amp;rdquo;, but you don&amp;rsquo;t need to install Go to enjoy Stencil. Just grab a precompiled binary!
Stencil is written in Go with support for multiple platforms. The latest release can be found at Stencil Releases.
Stencil currently provides pre-built binaries for the following:
macOS (Darwin) for x64, i386, and ARM architectures Windows Linux Stencil may also be compiled from source wherever the Go toolchain can run; e.</description></item><item><title>Module Quick Start</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/module-quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/module-quick-start/</guid><description>This quick start assumes you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with stencil usage already. If you aren&amp;rsquo;t be sure to go through the reference documentation or the quick start.
Step 1: Create a module Using the stencil create command we&amp;rsquo;re able to quickly create a module, let&amp;rsquo;s start with a simple hello world module.
create-module.sh mkdir helloworld; cd helloworld stencil create module github.com/yourorg/helloworld You&amp;rsquo;ll notice that when running that command, stencil itself was ran.</description></item><item><title>Native Extension Quick Start</title><link>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/native-extension-quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://engineering.outreach.io/stencil/getting-started/native-extension-quick-start/</guid><description>This quick start assumes you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with stencil and module usage already. If you aren&amp;rsquo;t be sure to go through the reference documentation or the other quick starts here before proceeding. You&amp;rsquo;ve been warned!
What is a Native Extension? Native extensions are special module types that don&amp;rsquo;t use go-templates to integrate with stencil. Instead they expose template functions written in another language that can be called by stencil templates.</description></item></channel></rss>